Guide to the Cherry Tree Yearbook records, 1908-2005 RG0113
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Cherry Tree Yearbook records
1908-2008
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0113
73.25 Linear Feet
Collection includes Cherry Tree yearbooks, photographs from the Cherry Tree of buildings, students groups, events, clubs, departments, presidents, etc.
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open for use, with the exception of the series of yearbooks. Researchers are directed to use the copies located in the Special Collections reading room instead.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Cherry Tree Office.
Historical or Biographical Note
Originally called The Columbiad in 1890, the yearbook became The C in 1904, The Mall in 1905, and finally the Cherry Tree in 1908.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection consists primarily of photographs from the Cherry Tree of buildings, students groups, events, clubs, departments, presidents, etc. It also includes a set of extra copies of the yearbook which may be deaccessioned as needed.
Collection Organization
Organized into 10 series: one series of yearbooks, one of office files, and eight series of photogoraphs
Existence and Location of Copies
Two copies of the Cherry Tree Yearbook and its predecessors are cataloged in the main library catalog under LD 1947.C5. One of these copies is located in the Special Collections reading room, and the other is stored in the Special Collections' closed stacks area.
The yearbooks have been digitized and are available online at the Internet Archive.
Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Photographs; Washington (D.C.); Cherry Tree; Events; Mall, The (Washington, D.C.); Yearbooks; Students; George Washington University
- Office files, 1939-2000; RG0113 Series 1; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains correspondence, a poster, a postcard, a list and forms. They range in date from 1939 to 2000. The materials concern ordering yearbooks, taking pictures, information to accompany pictures, and requiting new employees.
  - Student publications - Cherry Tree, 1939-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1993-1994; RG0113 Series 2; 12 Linear feet
  Photos and negatives for 1993-1994 yearbook - concerts, athletics, students, aids quilt, sororities/fraternaties, cheerleaders, GW mascot, black people's union, buildings, campus scenes, theater, engineers egg drop, events, faculty/staff, fall festival/spring fling, greek life, homecoming, honors program, international week, President Trachtenberg, President Elliott, President Bush, President Gorbachev, Vaclav Havel, Shimon Perez, speakers, student association, chalk-in, troubadours, etc.
- Photographs and yearbook materials, 1994; RG0113 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Yearbook photos and materials for 1994
  - Photos: historical and graduation, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stephen Joel Trachtenberg, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Aerial photo, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - Students in class, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
    General note
    Labeled "Stud."
  - Man and woman examining a mechanical device, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - Two men and a woman in caps and gowns, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Group of men and women playing cards. Includes on man in what appears to be a military uniform, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.6)
    Labeled "W2."
  - Man and woman in cap and gown, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.7)
  - A formal dance, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.8)
  - Stephen Joel Trachtenberg and others on stage at convocation, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.9)
  - Oswald Symister Colclough, 1959-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
    Labeled "Acting.
  - Group recording in a sound studio, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.11)
  - Two women in nurses' uniforms assisting another woman lying with eyes closed--practicing first aid?, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.12)
  - Women in uniforms standing in front of Staughton Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.13)
  - Two men and a woman in caps and gowns, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.14)
    Duplicate of 00001.00005
  - Howard L. Hodgkins, 1921-1923 (Box 1, Folder 1.15)
  - Group of male students in chemistry class, including several in military uniforms, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.16)
  - George Washington Statue, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - profile, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
    Labeled "YB '94."
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - front view, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - profile, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - front view, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - three quarters view, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - profile, closeup, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - three quarters view, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - front view, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - front view, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2.9)
  - Photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Group portrait of the GW Band, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Group portrait of the GW Band, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Photo of statue of George Washington on Law School quad - front view, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Portrait of male student, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
    Labeled "Ellen"
  - Photo of metal bas-relief of George Washington, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - Two men below sign "Mr Henrys", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - Two men on city street below sign "Treviso Ristorante", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - Person on phone, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - Group photo posing on Albert Einstein statue, Constitution Ave and 22nd St NW., undated (Box 1, Folder 3.9)
    Labeled "Yearbook Staff '94."
  - Photo of person holding a 1994 yearbook, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.11)
    11 plastic sleeves
  - Jostens materials including cover mockup, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sample Cover of yearbook, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1994; RG0113 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  1994 Cherry Tree yearbook photos
  - Photos 1-30, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photos 31-60, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photos 61-90, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photos 91-120, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photos 121-150, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photos 151-180, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Photographic prints and negatives, undated; RG0113 Series 5; 33 Linear feet
  Photos and negatives from yearbooks
- Photographs, 1998-2002; RG0113 Series 6; 3.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5, Box 4)
  Photos from Cherry Tree - buildings, student groups, events, clubs, departments, President Trachtenberg, commencements, Dalai Lama, Hillary Clinton, faculty, sports, dormitories, Georgetown sites, Mount Vernon Campus, etc., 1998-2002
  - Academic Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Competition Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accountancy Department, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Sciences, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Walk, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AIESEC, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - All Star Basketball, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alpha Chi Sigma, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Reunion, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Marketing Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Student Dental Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anthropology Department, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arab Student Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Art Department, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Art Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Art Therapy, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Asian Student Alliance, 702:F3 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Band at Basketball, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bangladesh Cultural Society, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Baseball, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bell Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beta Alpha Psi, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Blues Traveler, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Biology Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Biology Department, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bob Chernak, VP, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bob Woodward at Family Weekend, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bowling Fundraiser Child Assistance International, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bridget Cooper, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campaigning for SA President, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Camping Trip, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Campus scenes - miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Caf Gelman, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Campus Cleanup, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Caribbean Students, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chalk-In, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chat at HOVA with B-Ball coaches, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cheerleaders, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cheerleaders at Safeway, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Chemistry Department, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cherry Tree Office, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Chinese American Students Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Circle K, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Civil and Environmental Engineering, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Class Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Classics Department, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - College Democrats, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - College Republicans, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Colonial Inauguration, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Commencement, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Commencement - Business School Ceremony, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Commencement - Desmond Tutu, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Commencement - Engineering Ceremony, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commencement - Law, with William Renquist, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commencement - Medicine, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commencement - School of Public Health, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Communication Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Community Service, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Convocation (opening of academic year), undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Counseling Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Crossfire news program from Media and Public Affair building, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dalai Lama, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dance Performance, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Daniel Small, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Day of Silence for Iraqi Children, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - DC Mayoral Debate, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dean Mazzuchi, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Deans of Columbian School, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Delores Stafford, Director of Campus Safety/Police, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Delta Sigma Pi Professional Business Fraternity, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Delta Sigma Theta MV beta chapter, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dennis Blumer, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Diane Bell, Women's Studies, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Diversions Sunana, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Diwali, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Donald Lehman, VP for Academic Affairs, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Double-Decker Colonial Bus, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - DJ's Fast Break, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Grier at American Meridian, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - East Asian Language and Literature, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - English as a Foreign Language (EFL), undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - English Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Engineers Council, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Elliot School (ESIA) Groundbreaking, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Excellence in Student Life Awards Dinner, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Fall Fest, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Fashion Show, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Fencing Club, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Festival, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Field Hockey, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Finance Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Floor Hockey, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Forensic Science, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Funger Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - G Street, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Gelman Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Geography Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Geology Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - George Washington University Hospital (old), Main Entrance, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - George Washington's Birthday celebration in the University Yard, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Georgetown sites, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - German and Slavic Language and Lit, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - German Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Golden Key NHS, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Greek Midnight Bingo (Religion Week), undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Greek Week Skit Night, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GW Band, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - GW Blitz, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GW Journal, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - GW National Law Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - GW Pride, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - GW Vibes, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - GWing Contest, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - GW-Monopoly, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Harey Tortoise Running Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hall of Government, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hall on Virginia Avenue, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hatchet, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hawaii Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Harry Harding, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Health and Wellness Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Helen Cannady, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hillel, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hillel Festival of Sukkot, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Hippotones, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - History Department, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Housing Lottery, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ice Sculptures, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - IMF/World Bank Protests, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Indian Dance Performance, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Indian Student Association, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - International Affairs, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - International Business, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - International Education Association, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - International Fair, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - International Night, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - International Services Office, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - International Student Society, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Interning, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Iranian Cultural Society, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - ISA, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - ISA Divali Dinner and Show, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Jack Krancz, Director of Athletics and Recreation, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Jay Leno, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Jean Folkerts, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Jill Kasle, University Marshall, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Jitterbugs Swing Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - John F. "Skip" Williams, VP, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Johnnie Osborne, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Jonathan Chaves, East Asian Languages, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Judaic Studies Department, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma (Gamma Chi Chapter), undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Kogan Plaza - Construction of Gazebo, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Kogan Plaza - Dedication, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Kogan Plaza - AIDS Walk, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Kogan Plaza and Gelman Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Lambda Chi Alpha, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Latinos for Progress, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lecture on Mount Vernon Campus with Pat Schroeder, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lester Lefton, CCAS Dean, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Linda Donnels, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lisa Ann Deply, Event Management, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Hall, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lou Katz, Executive VP, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Management Science (Naval Science), undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Marketing Department, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Martha's Marathon, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Awards, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Marvin Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Marvin Center - Interiors, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Marvin Center Hippodrome, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Mary Futrell, Dean of School of Education and Human Development, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Mascots, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mathematics Department, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mechanical Engineering, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Media and Public Affairs building (MPAB) - construction, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Media and Public Affairs building (MPAB) - opening, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball - practice, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Dayton, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Maryland, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Rhode Island, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Men's Basketball vs. St. Bonaventure, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Temple, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Men's Basketball vs. U. of Mass, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Virginia Tech, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Men's Crew, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Men's Cross-Country Team, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Men's Golf, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Men's Soccer, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Men's Tennis, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Michael Freedman, VP for Communications, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Midnight Breakfast, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Midnight Madness, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Mike Gargano, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Ministry of the Unreal, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Mock Trial, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Monumental Celebration Graduation Party at Union Station, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mount Vernon Campus, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mount Vernon Family Pumpkin Carving, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Moving-In Day to Dorms, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Music Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NAACP, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Naval Science, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Neighbors Project, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - New Hall, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NSCS, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Odyssey Cruise, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Old Main, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Oliver North, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Oktoberfest, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Omicion Delta Kappa Officials, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Organization of African Students, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Pakistani Students Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Parliamentary Debate Society, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Patricia Ireland, Former President of NOW, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Peter Konwerski, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Phi Sigma Pi, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Philippine Cultural Society, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Philosophy Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Physics Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Pitches, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - President Trachtenberg and Hillary Clinton, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Presidential Election night, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Professors Gate, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Program Board, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Progressive Student Union, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Project Exploration, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Psi Chi Psychology National Honor Frat, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Psychology Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Psychology Honors Fraternity Group Shot, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Public Administration, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Pumpkin Carving (Foggy Bottom), undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Puskin Statue Dedication, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Rajvee, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Recess, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Religion Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Residence Halls, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Residence Hall Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Richard Riegelman, School of Public Health, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Riverside Hall Council, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Rodney Johnson, Parent Services, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Romance Language Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Sailing Club, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - SASS Fun Day - Mt. Vernon Campus, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - School of Media and Public Affairs, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - September 11th Vigil, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Senior Week, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Sigma Delta Tau, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Sigma Kappa Zeta Chapter, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Sigma Nu (Delta Pi Chapter), undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Sikh Student Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Speech and Hearing Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Sociology Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - South Asian Society, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Spring Fling, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Statistics, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Stephen Joel Trachtenberg, GW President, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Steven Chough, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Student Admissions Representative Program (STAR), undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Stuart Hall, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Student Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Student Athlete Advisory Council, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Student Groups - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Student Network Admissions Program, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Students Scenes-Miscellaneous [1/2], undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Students Scenes-Miscellaneous [2/2], undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Students in Dorms, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Students in Kogan Plaza, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Study Abroad Fair, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Susan M. Phillips, Dean of School of Business And Public Administration, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Swim and Diving vs. JMU, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Tailgate Party, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Take Back the Night, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon (Alpha Pi chapter), undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Theatre and Dance Department, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Theta Tau Engineers, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Thurston Block Party, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - TKE Tau Kappa Epsilon, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Timothy Tong, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Toastmasters, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Tourism Department, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Trivia Club, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Troubadours, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Turkish Student Association, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Ultimate Frisbee, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - University Singers Group Shot, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - University Yard, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Vice President Gore Jobs Summit, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Volunteer Week, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Watermelon Fest, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Welcome Week College Democrats BBQ, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Whitewater, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Dayton, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Women's Basketball vs. La Salle, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Notre Dame, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Rutgers, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)